mihpay.com 2010-05-27

# Tradus.in - Privacy Policy

ibibo respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our web sites. 

In general, you can visit the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. [We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous.] 

Some of our web pages use "coolkies" so that we can better serve you with customized information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you. 

There are times when we may collect personal information from you such as name, physical address or telephone number. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. Generally, you will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit the Website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services. 

ibibo will not sell, trade or disclose to third parties any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service (including names and addresses) without the consent of the user or customer (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the user or others). ibibo will allow suppliers to access the information for purposes of confirming your registration and providing you with benefits you are entitled to. 

ibibo will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure. ibibo will continue to enhance its security procedures as new technology becomes available.

By accessing this site the user agrees to let ibibo and the assistants hired by ibibo store, process and use the personal data entered by the user to justify and administrate the business and User relationship, as well as to perform and execute deals and contracts initiated through the website. This particularly concerns the User’s name, address, telephone number, email address, sex and date of birth. 

_**Usage data**_

The User further agrees to let ibibo collect, process and use the User’s usage data in relation to usage of the Website with the help of electronic aids, in particular to design the Website and its presentation in terms of the user’s requirements, to encourage Website security and in order to make the services as optimum and secure as possible, this particularly concerns the user’s browser type (e.g. Explorer 5.x), operating system (e.g. Windows XP), internet domain and IP address.

**_Bank details_**

If the User enters their postal account and/or bank account information in their User account, they thus agree to let this data be used for any fee refunds from ibibo to the User, and for this data - insofar as the User has activated the relevant function in the user account - to be sent by email to the respective contractual partner after contract conclusion on the Website. 

**_Releasing of member names, place of residence, evaluations_**

The User agrees to let ibibo make their User names, the place of residence associated with the User names, registration date, evaluation profile and evaluation comments left by the User for other ibibo users visible to all visitors to the Website. The user is aware that non-disclosure of already published data is not possible. 

_**Publication of offers on the Website**_

The User agrees to the publication of information they enter when formulating an offer or as part of the “Questions & Answers” function or evaluation function. The User also agrees for their User name and (residential) base to be visible if they sell something on the Website. The User accepts that their telephone number will also be visible for offers in the form of classified ads. 

_**Publication of offers elsewhere**_

ibibo is authorised to publish offers, and the associated information released on the Website, on other platforms and in other media (e.g. newspapers) in the appropriate format. 

**_Forwarding of contact details after contract conclusion_**

The User agrees for ibibo to forward the stored contact data and a text entered by the user for this purpose, as well as the User’s postal and/or bank details - insofar as the User has activated this function in the User account - to the respective contractual partner for the purposes of executing a contract concluded through the Website. 

_**Forwarding as per legal regulations**_

In the event of a legal regulation, governmental order or preliminary official proceedings, ibibo is authorised, without further notice, to provide the respective data to the authorities, as required. 

_**Storage and usage after termination of membership**_

The User agrees for the data in the offer relating to their User name including but not limited to, details of products offered, the User’s place of residence and post code, bids placed by them etc. to be displayed on the Website even after the offer period is over. The User also agrees for their data to be stored and used for the abovementioned purposes even after membership has been terminated. It is particularly stated that received and submitted user evaluations will continue to remain visible and that legal data storage obligations exist.

If our privacy policy changes in the future, it will be posted here and a new effective date will be shown. You should access our privacy policy regularly to ensure you understand our current policies. If you have any questions regarding ibibo's Privacy Policy, please email us at  [traduscustomercare@ibibogroup.com ](mailto:traduscustomercare@ibibogroup.com)Please refer the privacy policy in your subject line. ibibo will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt. 

**This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.**
